Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
（西(にし)）ハァハァ ハァハァ…
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
（加藤(かとう)）いちばん帰りたいの…
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
俺なんだよね
（計）あっ…
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
It's the beginning of a brand new day
A day filled with hope
Open your heart to happiness
And look up at the big, blue sky
Listen to the voice on the radio
And fill your lungs
With the fragrant air
One! Two! Three! Let's go!
He Can't Shoot
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
The one who wants
to go home the most is me.
Nishi!
西！
Kato!
（岸本(きしもと)）加藤君 ムリよ！ 戻って！
You're not gonna make it! Come back!
Is he serious?
（北条(ほうじょう)）あいつ マジかよ？
Fuckin' moron!
（欣二(きんじ)）
バカが！ てめえも死んじまえ！
Fine, you can go die too!
How could you say stuff like that?
なんてこと言うの？
What?
ああ？ やっちまうぞ この巨乳が！
Hey, Miss Melons, don't make
me come over there and bang ya!
Kurono!
玄野(くろの)君 なんとかしてよ！ 加藤君を
Do something! You've gotta help Kato!
Stop!
やめろ！
NISHI!
西ーっ！
（西）やめろー！
STOP IT!
（加藤）西ーっ！
Nishi!
Grandma! My ears hurt!
（亮太(りょうた)）おばあちゃん お耳痛いよ
（カヨ）よしよし 大丈夫かい？
There, there. Are you okay?
Hey, you old ass, shut him up!
（北条）
ばばあ いいかげんにしろよ
But he says his ears are hurting...
（カヨ）でも この子 耳が痛いって
It's nothing.
（北条）何でもねえよ
There, there.
（鉄男(てつお)）それよりよ
あのバカ 死んだ …のか？
Forget about that.
There, there.
Oh you poor thing. Alright now...
What happened to that idiot...
Is he dead?
There, there. Easy now...
どっちだっていいさ そんなの
Who cares if he is or not?
Yeah! Serves him right!
（春哉(はるや)）ざまあみろ
I couldn't make it in time...
（加藤）間に合わなかった
（西）プハッ！
西！
（岸本・計）あっ！
Nishi!
こいつを殺して…
Kill him...
Doesn't give up easily, does he?
あいつ しぶといねえ
（欣二）
死んじゃえば良かったのにな
Ah, it woulda been better if he died.
Yuzo.
裕三(ゆうぞう)君？
SOMEBODY PLEASE KILL HIM!
誰か こいつを殺してくれー！
So we all can go back!
（西）
全員 帰れる！　俺も無傷で！
And so I can get back safe too!
Hurry!
（西）早く！
（せきこみ）
Do it quick!
早く！
（加藤）殺す？
Kill him?
Yuzo.
（鈴木星人）裕三君？
（エネルギーの上昇音）
Use your gun...
（西）銃で… 銃で撃て！
Shoot him!
加藤君 来るよ！ 逃げて 早く！
Kato!
He's coming! Get out of there! Hurry!
Kato! Run!
加藤 逃げろ！
お前 狙われてんぞ！
He's after you!
I...
そ… そうはいかない！
I can't!
Nishi...
西を… 西を助けないと！
（計）な… 何言ってんだ？
I have to save Nishi!
Are you out of your mind?
You idiot!
バカ野郎！ だったら早く撃て！
Then why don't you hurry up and shoot him?
He's right!
そうよ　逃げないんなら撃って！
そうじゃないと死んじゃうってば！
You gotta shoot him
if you're not going to run!
Otherwise you're going to die!
Shoot him! Do it now!
（岸本）撃って！ 早く！
What are you waiting for, Kato?
何してるのよ？ 加藤君
Kishimoto...
岸本 あいつ 撃てねえよ
He can't shoot it.
But... We don't have time for that!
でも
そんなこと言ってる場合じゃ…
I know it, and so does Kato...
（計）そんなことは分かってるよ
あいつだって よ～く分かってるさ
けど あいつは撃てない
そういうヤツなんだよ 昔から
But still...
He can't shoot!
That's just how Kato is...
and how he's always been.
俺だって まだ撃ったことない
I've never shot anyone myself,
but maybe one day I'll have to...
けど いつかは撃つかもしれない
だけど あいつは撃たない ずっと
（岸本）そんな…
But Kato, he won't fire that gun.
He'll never do it.
No way...
（計）俺…
計算高いヤなヤツに見えたかな？
Maybe that sounded
too cold and calculating.
I wasn't trying to talk trash about Kato
just because I want to do her.
別に 岸本とヤリたいから
加藤の悪口言ったわけじゃ…
いや 悪口じゃねえぞ
Nah, it's not like I said
anything bad about him anyway.
What I'm trying to tell her is that
Kato is too kind a person to shoot anyone.
俺は 加藤は優しいヤツだって
言いたかっただけで…
Kato...
加藤 ムリだ　お前 撃てない！
Give it up... You just can't shoot!
（岸本）加藤君 助けなきゃ！
We've gotta help Kato!
C'mon, guys! If we don't hurry, Kato will...
ねえ 早くしないと加藤君が…
フン！ なんで？
（春哉）自分で行け バ～カ！
Ha! Why should we?
Go do it yourself, moron!
Ah, fuck it! What the hell
are we doing here anyway?
アア… なんか どうでもいいや
なんで
こんな所にいるんだ？ 俺たち
Yeah, let's get outta here.
（春哉）帰ろうぜ
You too!
てめえもな
俺 殴ってる暇があったら―
If you got time to beat me up, why don't
you go help that fuckin' leader? Eh?
あのムカつくリーダー助けてやれや
ああ？
（鉄男）クッ…
（岸本）ちょ… ちょっと！
Wait!
Time for some ramen.
（欣二）ああ ラーメン ラーメン
（春哉）歯ぁ痛(いて)えや ちくしょう！
Shit, my mouth hurts...
亮太
おばあちゃんたちも行こうかね
Why don't we go too, Ryota?
Somebody... Please!
（岸本）誰か お願い！
Are you serious?
マジ？ こっちに振るのかよ？
You're going to look to me for help?
Fine then!
Whoa... Wait!
ちょ… ま…
（岸本）私が行く
I'll go!
I wanna help Kato...
加藤君 助けたいし
And I hate hearing you people say I'll die
unless I rely on someone else!
誰かに頼らないと死んじゃうなんて
言われたのも悔しいし
私が…
So...
I'll go do it myself.
行く
（計）待って
Wait!
俺が… 行くよ…
I'II...
I'll go.
ど… どうすればいい？
What should I do?
I know...
そうだ 脅しに使うんなら―
Maybe I can use this to keep him at bay.
動きも牽制(けんせい)できるかもしれない
フゥ…
Hey! Are you all right?
（加藤）おい！ 大丈夫か？
誰か… 聞こえない…
I can't... hear anyone...
軽い…
He's pretty light.
向こうまで 行けるか？
Can I make back over there?
Stop...
（西）動きを…
Stop moving...
（西）止めろ
（加藤）はぁ？
ウワッ！
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
あっ… 西！
Nishi!
Where's... Where's the gun?
じゅ… 銃は？
Yuzo!
裕三君？
Kato!
加藤！
加藤 …君？
Kato...
I missed...
外れ…
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
Kato!
加藤！
（岸本）加藤君？ 加藤君！
Kato...
Kato!
What the... hell just happened?
一体 どうなっちまったんだ？
Kato?
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
あっ…
（岸本）加藤君？
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
Bet they're all dead by now.
あいつら 今ごろ
みんなして死んでたりしてな
Like I give a shit!
おら 知らねえ
ああ それよりラーメンな ラーメン
All I want right now is some ramen!
Shut up.
うるせえよ
Oh yeah... You wanna
see a dentist first, right?
ああ
お前は歯医者が先か ヘヘッ…
（春哉）
チッ… こんな時間に開いてねえよ
What kind of dentist
would be open this late?
Grandma, I'm hungry.
（亮太）
おばあちゃん おなかすいたよ
Certainly, Ryota.
そうだね 亮太
Why don't we call your mother
and have her pick us up?
今から お母さんに電話して
車で迎えに来てもらおうか？
We'll have her pick up a hamburger
and you can eat it in the car.
途中で
ハンバーガー買ってきてもらおうね
そしたら
車の中で食べればいいから
（亮太）うん それなら いいよ
Okay! That sounds good!
It's the beginning of a brand new day
That's strange...
変だね　壊れてるのかしら？
I wonder if it's broken?
It's the beginning of a brand new day
A day filled with hope
Open your heart to happiness
Hey, kid!
（欣二）おい ガキ
なに見てやがんだ？ ああ？
What the hell are you looking at, huh? Jeez...
Open your heart to happiness
And look up at the big, blue sky
…たく
Hey, you got some smokes?
And look up at the big, blue sky
おい よう タバコ持ってねえか？
（春哉）ねえ！
And look up at the big, blue sky
Nope. Dropped 'em somewhere...
Listen to the voice on the radio
どっかに落とした
（欣二）マジかよ？
Are you kidding me?
Listen to the voice on the radio
And fill your lungs
Oh well... Time for ramen!
しゃあねえな　ラーメン ラーメン
With the fragrant air
One! Two! Three! Let's go!
C'mon, let's go.
（欣二）おい 早く行こう
One! Two! Three! Let's go!
Grandma...
おばあちゃん あのおにいちゃん…
That guy's head is... gone.
頭 なくなっちゃった…
Yes, yes, dear...
亮太ったら もう… ハッ！
Ryo... Ryota! Let's get out of here!
りょ… 亮太 出るのよ！
（亮太）痛い 痛いよ おばあちゃん
Ouch! You're hurting me, Grandma!
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
Kato! Are you all right?
（計）大丈夫か？ 加藤
Yeah... I think so.
（加藤）あ… ああ なんとか…
く… 玄野君 どうしよう？
Kurono...
Now what do we do?
Don't come! Don't come any closer!
（加藤）
近づかないほうがいい　近づくな！
What the hell is that?
何だ？ あれ
What's going on?
ど… どうなってる？
グエッ！ グエッ！
What a strange smell...
（岸本）変な におい…
（計）キ… キモイ
Gross...
What are we supposed to do now?
（加藤）これから どうすんだ？
Uh...
え… え～っと ネギ星人のとき…
Well, when we fought the Green onion Alien...
I think he used this one...
確か これ…
It's okay...
（計）
大丈夫　でかいけど鳥だ 鳥！
That thing is big,
but it's just a bird. Only a bird!
ただの鳥！
What's happening?
（加藤）
どうなってる？ 計ちゃん 何した？
What did you do, Kei?
Looks like that made it shoot up in the air...
（計）上に送ったらしい
（計）終わった…
It's over...
Yeah... It's over.
ああ 終わった
Nishi!
西… 西は？ 西！
Where's Nishi?
Nishi!
Hey, are you okay?
（加藤）おい 大丈夫か？
It's over!
終わったぞ
おい 聞こえないのか？
Hey! Can't you hear me?
痛え…
Oh... It hurts...
痛え… ウウッ…
It hurts...
His ears are bleeding...
（岸本）耳から血が出てる
（計）鼓膜やられたんじゃねえの？
I guess his eardrums burst.
We're going back
to that room now, right?
これから
また部屋に戻るんだよな？
（計）あっ そういや おかしいな
That's strange.
The last time the transporting
started right away...
前のときは
すぐ 送るやつ始まってたけどな
This is weird...
おかしいな…
どうして移動 始まらないの？
（計）変だな どうしてだろう？
Why isn't it transporting us back?
It's weird...
I wonder why...
Maybe it's not over yet.
まだ終わってねえんじゃねえのか？
（計）えっ？
な… なんで？
（岸本）そんな…
How come?
No way...
Maybe there are more.
（加藤）まだいるんじゃねえのか？
ネギ星人のときみたいに
Just like how it happened
with the Green onion Alien...
But... How can we be sure?
（計）そ…
でも どうやって確認すんだよ？
あのレーダーみたいなやつだ
What about that radar-like thing...
That's it! He should have it...
そうだ こいつが持ってたはずだ
Shit, no good.
くそ！ ダメだ　壊れてやがる
It's broken.
もしかして これか？
（加藤）持ってるのか？
Wait, are you talking about this thing?
You mean you have one?
I was right...
（加藤）
やっぱり そうだ　まだ１匹いる
There's one more.
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
What the fuck is going on?
（春哉）一体 どうなってんだ？
Kinji's head got blown off...
（春哉）欣二 頭飛んだぞ
何もしてねえのに…
Although he didn't do anything...
And he didn't even come across
that fuckin' alien or anything!
何とか星人に
出会ってもいねえのに！
（鉄男）マジかよ？
Is he serious?
So we can't go back
until we get the other one?
もう１匹捕まえねえと
帰れないのか？
Yeah...
I... I don't wanna die...
死にたくない…
C'mon, hurry...
早くしてくれ… ガンツ
Gantz...
Kato...
加藤
（加藤）計ちゃん どうした？
What's wrong, Kei?
His neck is broken...
こいつ 首… 折れてるぞ
（西）寒い… 寒い…
（岸本）寒いの？
Cold... I'm cold...
You're cold?
My neck is gone...
首… なくなった
I don't feel anything...
感覚ねえ…
This is the second time...
（西）２度目だ
Last time...
前に１回　俺 首１回…
I... My neck...
Before...
俺 首…
西丈一郎(じょういちろう)　中２　転落死
Joichiro Nishi, eight grader. I fell.
Fell?
転落死って…
On my own... My neck... I...
自分で首… 自分で…
Then... You mean you also...
（岸本）あなたも…
Gonna die... This is bad...
死ぬ…
ヤバイ もうすぐ死ぬ…
I'm gonna die soon.
I don't want to... die so soon...
（西）早く… 死にたくない…
No... I don't wanna die...
ヤダ　死ぬのイヤだ
Don't give up yet! Please!
まだ諦めないで！ お願い！
Don't say you're gonna die!
簡単に 死ぬなんて言わないで！
Kishimoto!
（計）岸本… そっか
お前 いちばん そう思うよな
That's right... You must understand
how he feels more than anybody else...
I never...
（西）誰も…
（計）あっ…
（西）嫌いじゃなかった
hated anyone...
I hated... society.
嫌いなの 世の中…
だって メチャクチャじゃん
Because it's all messed up...
I always felt...
（西）いっつも思ってた
that I need to stay on track.
俺だけは ちゃんとしないとって
But it's all fucked up...
（西）メチャクチャなんだよ
That's why I couldn't stay on track...
だから
ちゃんと できなかったんだよ
俺…
I...
I don't wanna die...
（西）ヤダ… 死ぬのイヤだ
I don't wanna...
I don't wanna die...
ヤダ　ママ…
Mom...
（西）ママ… 謝らないと…
I have to apologize to her...
Mom, I'm sorry.
ママ ごめん…
Mom, I tried hard but...
ママ 一生懸命…
でも…
Mom, I'm sorry!
ママ ごめん
I'm scared...
（西）こ… 怖いよ…
Mom, Mom... I'm cold.
アア… 寒い
Mom, I'm gonna die...
ママ 死んじゃうよ…
Hey, answer me!
（春哉）おい 答えろ！
Is there any way we can be free from this?
俺らが自由になる方法あんのかよ？
（鉄男）黙れ！
Shut the fuck up!
てめえのことばっか考えてねえで
これ よく見とけ　見とけ！
Stop being so goddamn selfish!
Take a good look at this! Look at it!
Mom...
ママ 100点…
100 points...
（西）点数…
My score...
I had 90 points...
90点集まってたんだよ
Just 10 more and I would have been free...
あと10点で…
自由になれたのに…
He's... dead.
（加藤）死んだ…
Pedestrians and
Bicyclists only
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
You probably think we're idiots, huh?
（春哉）てめえら
俺のことバカだと思ってんだろう？
いいぜ 別に
Well, no big deal, but listen.
I'm running things around here now.
けどな 今この場 仕切ってんの
俺なんだよな
You wanna get shot, Tetsuo?
撃たれてえのかよ？ ああ？ 鉄男！
Next time: "Kato, You Wait Here"
次回 “加藤くんは待っていて”